

PROFILE

I am Brandon Pizer, a second-year college student attending Colorado State University. My major is Ecosystem Science and Sustainability, and my minor is Geospatial Information Sciences (GIS).

I am very involved at Colorado State University. As a freshman, I was accepted into the Honors College, and I joined the Delta Chi Fraternity, acquiring a board position (Recruitment Chair) after only one semester.

I am a versatile worker, critical thinker, and multi-tasker who would be a great fit for any job or team.

CONTACT

PHONE: 310-755-5950

EMAIL: brandonpizer08@gmail.com

ACHIEVEMENTS

Seal of Biliteracy (Japanese)

Honor Roll

Honors College Scholarship

BRANDON PIZER

Student Intern for Hire

EDUCATION

South High School

August 2019 – June 2023

I was on the Honor Roll every semester and graduated with a weighted GPA above 4.0. I played Varsity Soccer for three years and was captain in my senior year. I was also on the executive board of two clubs during my time at South.

Colorado State University

August 2023 - Present

I am in my second year of college with the number of credits as a third year. I am studying Ecosystem Science and Sustainability with a minor in Geospatial Information Science. I am a member of the Honors College too..

EXPERIENCE

Ko-Ryu Ramen – Waiter, Busser, Food Runner

April 2023 - July 2023

During my senior year and summer, I worked as a food runner, busser, and host learning skills such as customer service and teamwork

Azusa Reality - Office Assistant

June 2022 – August 2023

I performed tasks such as file management and tech support. I learned skills such as time management and computer skills.

Delta Chi Fraternity – Recruitment and New Member EducationDecember 2023 – December 2024

I was elected to this position where I managed all recruitment operations and new membership for the calendar year.